Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Library, 1931-2013; 6 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes.
  - Wise, Nina. A big new free happy unusual life. New York: Broadway Books, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Zwehl-Burke, Pamela and Fedorchuk, Leslie. Women's Autobiographical Artists' Books. University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee Art Museum Fine Arts Galleries and the Conference Center of the Golda Meir Library, 1987 November (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Con el cuerpo por delante: 47882 minutos de performance. Mexico: Instituto Nacional de Bellas Artes, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Voices from the edge: conversations with Jerry Garcia, Ram Dass, Annie Sprinkle, Matthew Fox, Jaron Lanier & Others. California: The Crossing Press Freedom, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Find-A-Text Puzzle Fun: Art World Edition. New York: Art-Text Enterprises, 2008 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Aeroports Magazine. No. 8, 2006 March (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Americana. Vol. 6 No. 1, 1978 March-April (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Art in America, 1984 September (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Art in America, 2007 June-July (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Art in America, 2009 April (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Art in America, 2013 June-July (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Artforum. Vol. 22 No. 2, 1983 October (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Artforum. Summer, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - ArtLies, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Ascent. Issue 24, Winter, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Cabinet: A Quarterly of Art and Culture. Issue 14, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Camerawork. Vol. 30 No.1 Spring/Summer, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Crawl Out Your Window. Vol. 7, 1980 July (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Crawl Out Your Window. Vol. 9/10, 1982 May (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Dialogue: An Art Journal. Vol. 12 No. 4, 1989 July-August (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Dystonia. Vol. 12 No. 1, 2009 January (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Five Fingers Review. Issue 10, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Front. Vol. 14 No. 4, 2003 September-October (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Harpers. Vol. 279 No. 1670, 1989 July (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - LA Weekly. Vol. 35 No. 35, 2013 July (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Live. Issue 3, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Branca, Glenn. Live 6/7, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - New Observations. No. 112, Fall, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - New Observations. No. 108, 1995 September-October (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - New Performance. Vol. 1 No. 3, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - New Wilderness Letter. Vol. 2 No. 7, Summer, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - PAJ: A Journal of Performance and Art. Vol. 34 No. 1, 2012 January (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - PAJ: A Journal of Performance and Art. Vol. 23, No. 3, 2001 September (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Parachute. Issue 64, 1991 October (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Parachute. Issue 80, 1995 October-December (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Pasatiempo, 2013 February (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Performing Arts Journal. Vol. 4, No. 3 (Issue 12), undated (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Pform. No. 38, 1995-1996 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Pform. No. 45, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Profile. Vol. 4 No. 6, 1984 December (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - College of New Rochelle. Quarterly. Spring/Summer, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Satori. Vol. 1 No. 3, Winter, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Signature. Vol. 5 No. 2, Winter, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Spy: The New York Monthly, 1987 November (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Sulfur. Issue 22, Spring, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - The Act. Vol. 1 No. 3, 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - Center for Creative Photography. The Archive. No. 17, 1983 March (Box 100, Folder 33)
  - The Cherotic (r)evolutionary. Vol. 1 Issue 8, undated (Box 100, Folder 34)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 23 No. 1, 1979 March (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 30 No. 1, Spring, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 33 No. 1, Spring, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - The Drama Review: TDR. Vol. 56 No. 4, 2012 (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - The Dumb Ox. Issue 10/11, Spring, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 37)
  - The Sunday Times Magazine, 1984 July 1 (Box 100, Folder 38)
  - Ulster. Spring, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 39)
  - Working Paper. Issue 2, 1981 November (Box 100, Folder 40)
  - Creative Arts '67. University of Wisconsin, Spring, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Video Data Bank. Video Tape Review. Issue 86, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - 1ere Semaine Internationale de Video Geneve - Suisse, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - American Film Institute. National Video Festival: Olympic Screenings, 1984 September (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Artists Space. Unacceptable Appetites, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Arts Society of Kingston. Kingston Sculpture Biennial, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Cohn, Terri. Artist's Response: Portraits and Self-Portraits, 2010 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Everson Museum of Art. Figures: Form and fiction, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts. Rapture: The body, ritual + sacred practice. London, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Montano, Linda. Pinata Project, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Museo de Arte Contemporaneo. Como virir juntos: Selection 27a Bienal de Sao Paulo, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco Art Institute. The Annual: September 12, 1975 - August 27, 1976, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Singh, Victoria (Ed.). Ritual in contemporary performance: Western front performance art contemporary ritual series, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Everson Video Revue, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Personal Histories, 1988 March (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Love and kisses from Annie Sprinkle: volume 2. New York, Gates of Heck, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Love and kisses from Annie Sprinkle: volume 1. New York: Gates of Heck, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Santa Cruz film festival program, 2008 May (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Zen Mountain Center of New York. Mountain Record. Summer, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Zen Mountain Center of New York. Mountain Record. Fall, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Ananda Ashram: Yoga Society of New York. Summer Program Guide, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Center for Creative Photography. Annual Report, 2011-2012 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - The Minnette Files. San Francisco: The Lab, 2000 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Almanac Weekly, October 2013 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Almanac Weekly, October 2012 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - ALOP, 2011 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - And/Or Notes, March 1980 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Art Times, Spring 2013 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Artist's Body, The, 2000 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - B., Franko. Franko B: Blinded by Love, 2007 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Beverly Ogdon on Swinging, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Binnewater Tides, The, Fall 1992 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Binnewater Tides, The, Summer 1991 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Rail, The, February 2012 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Bry, Doris. Alfred Stieglitz: Photographer, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Chronogram, May 2014 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Chronogram, December 2008 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Rail, The, July-August 2013 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Chronogram, January 2013 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Chronogram, September 2013 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Chronogram, October 2000 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Chronogram, October 2010 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Chronogram, July 2007 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Chronogram, September 2013 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Chronogram, October 2009 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Chronogram, March 2007 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Chronogram, June 2006 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Ear Magazine, November 1982-January 1983 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Ear Magazine, June-August 1981 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - East Bay Express, May 2012 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Explore Hudson Valley, October 2012 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Flue (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Furnace. Sex, Performance, and the 80s, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Goldberg, Roselee. Performance, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Hallwalls, December 1996 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Heart Before Art/Life Counseling, A, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - High Performance V.7 No. 3 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - High Performance V.7 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - HIgh Performance V.5 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - HIgh Performance V.8 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 2 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - HIgh Performance V.5 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - HIgh Performance V.6 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - HIgh Performance V.6 No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - HIgh Performance V.12 No. 2 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - HIgh Performance V.12 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - HIgh Performance V.8 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - HIgh Performance V.6 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - HIgh Performance V.7 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - HIgh Performance V.7 No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - HIgh Performance V.1 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - HIgh Performance V.3 No. 3 and 4 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - HIgh Performance V.4 No. 1 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - HIgh Performance V.4 No. 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - HIgh Performance V.13 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - HIgh Performance V.4 No. 4 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - HIgh Performance V.11 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - HIgh Performance V.11 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - HIgh Performance V.2 No. 3 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - HIgh Performance V.9 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 1 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 3 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - HIgh Performance V.10 No. 4 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - HIgh Performance V.11 No. 1 and 2 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Italian Cooking, 2011 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - La momelle, Spring 1976 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Magazine, The, February/March 2013 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Magazine, The, April 2013 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Magazine, The, May 2013 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Montano, Lina M. The Art/life institute handbook (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Montano, Linda M. Letters from Linda M. Montano, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Montano, Linda M. Performance artists of the eighties, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Montano, Linda M. Profile, December 1984 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Montano, Linda M. The Wisdom of Mataji & Bapuji, February 2000 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Montano, Linda M. The Wisdom of Mataji & Bapuji, February 2000 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Montano, Linda. Art in Everyday Life, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Montano, Linda. Performance artists talking in the eighties, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Montano, Linda. The 5 Johns of John Street (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Montano, Linda. The 5 Johns of John Street (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Montano, Linda. Twelve Poems (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Munroe, Alexander. The Third Mind, 2009 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - N. Paradoxa, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - N. Paradoxa, 2015 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Pauline's Proverbs, Christmas 1976 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Power of Feminist Art, The, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Santa Fe Reporter, February 2013 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe Reporter, May 2013 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Schimmel, Paul. Out of actions, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Signature, Spring 1967 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Site-Specific Artworks, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Hardcore from the Heart, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Love Vibration, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Post Porn Modernist, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Sprinkle, Annie. Spectacular Sex, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Theories and documents of contemporary art, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Theory and Flesh, Winter 1986 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Theory and Flesh, April 1986 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Theory and Flesh, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Theory and Flesh, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Theory and Flesh, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Unison, October 1989 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Unison, April-July 1988 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Vision, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Wack!, 2007 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Wasserman, Marion Claire. Prana, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Weirmeir, Jude. Issue 19, 2013 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Wine Wise, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Series XIII: Archived Websites, February 2016-ongoing; 2 websites in 2 archived websites.
  Appraisal
  Robots.txt (a piece of code that prevents crawlers from advancing through a site) were ignored during capture with the permission of the site owner.
  There were six videos included on Linda Montano's website that were not present on the hard drive associated with this collection. These were crawled separately to ensure adequate capture.
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.lindamontano.com and http://lindamarymontano.blogspot.com in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  This series contains Linda Montano's website and blog. The website contains her biography; descriptions of her films and books; personal photos and images of her performance art; her CV; the 14 YEARS OF LIVING ART digital exhibit and the follow-up, ANOTHER 21 YEARS OF LIVING ART (1998-2019); Chakra Prayers digital exhibit; program descriptions and needs for performances; and information on the wish list project. The blog features Montano's reflections and musings on topics related to her performance art, gender, politics, and spirituality. The site has posts dating back to 2009. It also includes interviews with Montano, speeches, images and videos from her performances. The blog also documents her impersonations of Mother Teresa and Bob Dylan and collaborations with Tehching Hsieh and Pauline Oliveros.
- OVERSIZE Series I: Art Practice
  - OVERSIZE Subseries A: Art Administration
    - Oversize Handwritten Performance Ideas, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries B: Writing
    - 7 Chakra Flower Prayers, undated (Box 81)
    - "7 Chakras Prayers", undated (Folder 12)
    - 7 Years of Living Art Performance Posters, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Title Page, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 1-8, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 9- 15, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 16- 24, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 25- 32, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 33- 40, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 41- 48, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 49- 56, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 57- 64, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 65-72, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 73- 80, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 81- 88, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 89- 96, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 97- 104 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 105- 112, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 113- 120, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 121- 128, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 129- 136, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 137- 144, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Art In Everyday Life Annotated Galley Proof: Pages 145- 152, [1981] (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Photo for Galleys: You Too Are a Performance Artist, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - "System:matic Extracises", undated (Box 81)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries D: Press
    - Promotional Posters, 1980-1989 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Promotional Posters, 1990-1999 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Promotional Posters, 2000-2013 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Posters, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Promotional Posters, 1989-2002 (Folder 13)
      Snug Harbor Cultural Center "Outside the Frame: Performance and the Object," Exit Art "The End Is the Beginning," University Gallery Events and Exhibitions Poster, and Exit Art "Reactions."
    - Publicity: La Mamelle Performance Vol. 1, No. 4 and The Brooklyn Rail, Feb. 2012, 1976, 2012 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries F: Photos
    - 7 Years of Living Art Photograph, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Annotated Photograph Album, [1942-1970] (Box 84)
    - Chicken Photograph, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Dandelion Photograph, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Linda Photograph by Mitchell, undated (Box 81)
    - Linda Portrait by Paul, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - "Montano Oliveros" Photo, undated (Folder 10)
    - Performance Photos: "Rosita" by Barbara Spohr, 1980, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Performance Portraits by Ana Barrado, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Personal Photos - Oversize, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Untitled Performance Photo Series, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Untitled Performance Photos, undated (Box 73, Folder 11, Box 85, Folder 26)
  - OVERSIZE Subseries G: Artworks
    - 7 Outfits for "Chakra Girl", 1999 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - 7 Years of Living Art / 7 Chakras Polaroid Collage, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Aluminum Plate for Art in Everyday Life Cover, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - "Angst", undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - "Beggary Again", 1965, undated (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Chakras: 7 Years of Living Art Transparent Drawings, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Collage Scrapbook, undated (Box 82)
    - "Dear Buyer of Hannah Wilke Sculpture..." Tit Print, undated (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - "The Call", undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Chicken Photographs [1 of 2], undated (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Chicken Photographs [2 of 2], undated (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Chicken Sketches, August 1968 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - "December 20, 30 Pigeons, 9:30 AM" Drawings [1 of 2], 1969, undated (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - "December 20, 30 Pigeons, 9:30 AM" Drawings [2 of 2], 1969, undated (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - "Encounter!", April 1965 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Extra Shoe Drawings [1 of 4], undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Extra Shoe Drawings [2 of 4], undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Extra Shoe Drawings [3 of 4], undated (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Extra Shoe Drawings [4 of 4], undated (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Figure Sketches [pencil, pen, watercolor], undated (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - "Flower Time", undated (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - "Forest Time" or "Verdunt I", 1965, undated (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - House Drawing, undated (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - "I Have Tried To Give My Love To You...", undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Landscape Watercolors, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Linda Self Portrait, undated (Box 81)
    - Occupy Wall Street Sign: "Compassion is the New Currency" Performance at St. Patricks NYC, undated (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #1, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #2, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #3, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #4, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #5, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #6, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #7, undated (Box 82)
    - Oil Painting Portrait #8, undated (Box 82)
    - Plastic Chicken Print, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - "Play Life", undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Religious Sketches, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Shoe Series: "Camera Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Shoe Series: "Cat Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Shoe Series: "Chicken Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Shoe Series: "Feather Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Shoe Series: "Feather Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Shoe Series: "Feminist Shoe, or S.C.U.M.", undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Shoe Series: "Flat Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Shoe Series: "Floating Girl Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Shoe Series: "Girl Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Shoe Series: "Girl Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Shoe Series: "House Shoe", undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Shoe Series: "Men-Women Cork-Cloth Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Shoe Series: "Piano Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Shoe Series: "Pigeon Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Shoe Series: "Red Charger Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Shoe Series: "Sad Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Shoe Series: "Sling Back Wood Heel Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Shoe Series: "Toe Open Shoe", undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #1, undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #2, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #3, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #4, undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #5, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #6, undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #7, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #8, undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Shoe Series: Untitled Shoe #9, undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Shoe Series: "Wing Shoe", undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - "Tongue to Flowers" Linda by Mitchell, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Untitled [ink], undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Untitled [Bird Paintings], undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Untitled [Flower Painting], undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Untitled [Green Painting], undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Untitled [Hand Painting], undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Untitled Pastel Work [Child Portrait], undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Untitled [People Paintings], undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Untitled [Sun], undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Untitled [Sunset Painting], undated (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Untitled [Sunset Painting], undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Untitled [Watercolor], undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Untitled Works, undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Watercolor Portraits, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Inspirational People and Collaborators
  - Annie Sprinkle: 7 Chakra Poster, undated (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Annie Sprinkle California Tit Print, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Annie Sprinkle Chakras Target Practice Painting, undated (Folder 11)
  - Annie Sprinkle Health/Sex Worker Poster, [2002] (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Annie Sprinkle: Linda Montano Character Portraits [1 of 2], undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Annie Sprinkle: Linda Montano Character Portraits [2 of 2], undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Annie Sprinkle Linda Montano Polaroid Collage, undated (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Annie Sprinkle: Linda Montano Portraits, undated (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Annie Sprinkle Performance Photos of Linda, [March 1991] (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Annie Sprinkle Photo: Linda Montano as Guru, undated (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Annie Sprinkle Playing Cards and Earth Manifesto, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Love Art Laboratory: Annie Sprinkle Wedding Invitations [1 of 2], 2003-2010 (Box 74, Folder 23)